[Music]
triplets born the throne awaits a seer
wounds of a deadly fate give up your
children separate by your time the lion
way
[Music]
we'll be found
the children grow
learn what's right leaders of the
freedom fight they seek their mother she
knows they do
will the prophecy come true
I long for my children but I have to
wait to act too soon could seal their
fate they made a bow
we'll be found Sonic Underground let's
board the throne awaits a few ones of a
deadly fate give up your children
separate by your time flying away
five
let me
Wow their mother
[Music]
learn what's right leaders of the
freedom fight they seek their mother she
knows they do is it time
you will the poppers she come true
I long for my children but I have to
wait to act too soon could seal their
fate
we'll be found
[Music]
let's board the throne awaits a few ones
of a deadly fate give up your children
separate by your time the lion weighs
ever
[Music]
their mother will be fine
the children grow
learn what's right leaders of the
freedom fight they seek their mother she
knows they do is it time and she
will the prophecy come true
my children but I have to wait to act
too soon could seal their face they made
a bow their mother will be found
[Music]
let's board the throne awaits a seer
warns of a deadly fate give up your
children separate by your time flying
away
Underground
learn what's right leaders of the
freedom fight they seek their mother she
knows they do is it time
if you don't leave you will the prophecy
come true
I long for my children but I have to win
to act too soon could seal their fate
they made a bow
b-bomb Sonic Underground
[Music]
let's board the throne awaits a seer
warns of a deadly fate give up your
children separate by your time The Lying
way
[Music]
they made
Wow their mother will be bow
children learn what's right leaders of
the freedom fight they seek their mother
she knows they do is it time it's
will the publish eat come true
I long for my children but I have to
wait to act too soon could seal their
fate they made a bow
we'll be bound Sonic Underground
[Music]
that's born the throne awaits a few ones
of a deadly fate give up your children
separate by your time flying away
Underground
Wow
Wow their mother will be fine
[Music]
learn what's right leaders of the
freedom fight they seek their mother she
knows they do
I'm concealed
well the prophecy come true
I long for my children but I have to
wait to act too soon could seal their
fate they made about
we'll be found Sonic Underground porn
the throne awaits the seer ones of a
deadly fate give up your children
separate by your time